Dayoung Kim

Jr. Front-end Web Developer

Address	Gyeongsangdo, South Korea
Mobile	+82 10 2869 7886
Email	kimdayoung771 @gmail.com
LinkedIn	https://www.linkedin.c om/in/dayoung-clara- kim/
Github	https://github.com/Day oung3460
Portfolio	https://dayoungportfoli o.netlify.app

PERSONAL SUMMARY

Junior Front-End Developer experiencing in a company that develops and services a blockchain-based platform. Skilledin developing and testing multiple web-based applications. Gained skills in aligning designs with clientrequirements and experience in resolving conflicts with colleagues professionally. Specializes in vanilla JavaScript and vue.js framework. Willing to learn native mobile development.

EDUCATION

programming academy, Deagu, Mar 2020 ~ Sep 2020

KEY SKILLS

- HTML
- CSS / Bootstrap
- JavaScript / jQuery
- Vue.js
- React.js
- Git(Github, Gitlab)
- TypeScript
- Kotlin
- JetBrains, Webstorm

WORK HISTORY

Coinvest – Gyeongsan-si, South Korea Junior Front-end web developer

: Nov 2020 ~ Present

- Collaborated with a design team to resolve CSS issues.
- Designed pages and components
- Turned design pages and components into vue.js
- Cooperated with back-end team to make API specification.
- UBIT and BES, Cryptocurrency Exchange Website (Jun 2021 ~ Present)
- Managed cryptocurrency exchange website development projects from initial design
- Used vue.js framework, Rest API(axios) and Web Socket
- Received real-time transaction data and drew a graph using Trading View chart library
- P2P exchange
- Library used:
 - > qrcode for OTP login
 - big-js to calculate big decimal
 - vue-i18n for translation
 - vue-router
 - vue-socket.io
 - > vuex
- Jangboda, a traditional market delivery application (Nov 2020 ~ May 2021)
- Developed and maintained webview for hybrid application.
- Used vue.js framework and Rest API(axios)
- Utilized Kakao map open API
- Applied NICE open API for user authentication
- Recorded average 500+ monthly active users